{
    "subject": "resource/Siege_of_Aintab",
    "predicate": "ontology/commander",
    "object": "resource/\u015eefik_\u00d6zdemir",
    "human_readable": "The commander of the Siege of Aintab was \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9443686008453369,
            "question": "What type of role did \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir have during the Siege of Aintab?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9401460289955139,
            "question": "Who was the commander of the Siege of Aintab?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8791064620018005,
            "question": "Who commanded the troops during the Siege of Aintab?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8679479956626892,
            "question": "What event was \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir in command of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8435418009757996,
            "question": "Which historical siege involved \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7672314047813416,
            "question": "Who led the forces during the Siege of Aintab?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7361527681350708,
            "question": "Name a military leader who participated in the Siege of Aintab."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5900518298149109,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a notable military campaign involving \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5526921153068542,
            "question": "Was \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir involved in any major sieges?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38084542751312256,
            "question": "What significant role did \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir play in history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The commander of the Siege of Aintab was \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3582_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir involved in any major sieges?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3582_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about a notable military campaign involving \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3582_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a military leader who participated in the Siege of Aintab.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3582_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3582_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There is no mention of a person named \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir in any of the documents.\n* However, document 19.txt mentions that the Battle of Aintab was fought in August of 1150, and was led by the King of Jerusalem, King Baldwin III.\n\nSo, based on this analysis, I would say that:\n\n* The commander of the Siege of Aintab is not mentioned to be \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir in the provided documents.\n\nTherefore, the answer is:\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: There is no information provided in the given context about \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir being the commander of the Siege of Aintab. The documents discuss various historical events and conditions in Aintab but do not mention this specific individual or his role during any sieges."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context that suggests or indicates that the commander of the Siege of Aintab was \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir or a Siege of Aintab being led by anyone in the provided text.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of a \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir being involved in the Siege of Aintab throughout the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The provided context does not mention \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir or any specific commander of the Siege of Aintab. The text discusses historical events and figures such as Ibrahim Pasha, Nur ad-din Zangi, and Ahmed Hur\u015fid Bey, but there is no information to support the existence of a commander named \u015eefik \u00d6zdemir during the siege of Aintab.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}